Unknown: It's part of the attention. One side of his cheeks almost caves in thinking. Lamont perhaps they did at first. The first photograph the first magazine, The gratified surge, The seeing themselves as others see them, The head geography of image, perhaps, perhaps the first time enjoyment After that, do you trust me? Trust me, They do not feel what you burn for. After the first surge, They care only that their photographs seem awkward or unflattering. Or and true, or that their privacy This thing you burn to escape what they call their privacy is being violated. Something changes After the first photograph has been in a magazine. The famous men do not enjoy their photographs and magazines so much as they fear that their photograph will cease to appear in magazines. They are trapped just as you are. Is this supposed to be good news? This is awful news. Lamont Are you willing to listen to a remark about what is true? Okey dokey. The truth will set you free, but not until it is finished with you. Maybe I ought to be getting back. Lamont The world is very old. You have been snared by something untrue. You are diluted. But this is good news. You have been snared by the delusion that envy has a reciprocal. You assume that there is a flip side to your painful envy of Michael Chang, namely, Michael Chang's enjoyable feelings of being envied by Lamont chew. No such animal animal, you burn with hunger for food that does not exist.
This is good news.
It is the truth to be envied. admired is not a feeling, nor is fame a feeling. There are feelings associated with fame, but few of them are any more enjoyable than the feelings associated with envy of fame. The burning doesn't go away. What fire dies when you feed it, It is not fame itself. They wish to deny you here, trust them. There is much fear and fame, terrible and heavy fear to be pulled and held carried. Perhaps they want only to keep it off you until you weigh enough to pull it toward yourself. What I sound like grateful of I said this doesn't make me feel very much better at all. Lamott. The truth is that the world is incredibly, incredibly, unbelievably old. You suffer with the stunted desire caused by one of its oldest lies, do not believe the photographs. fame is not the exit from any cage. So I was stuck in the cage from either side, fame or tortured envy of fame, there's no way out. You might consider how escaped from a cage must surely require foremost awareness of the fact of the cage. And I believe I see a drop on your temple right there.
Relevant infinite just excerpt number two.
But perhaps one does attain this to win. Imagine you you have become just what you have given your life to be not merely very good, but the best, The good philosophy of here and shit. I believe this philosophy of Enfield is more Canadian than American. So you may see I have prejudice is that you must have also. So leave to one side for a moment the talent and work to become best that you are doomed. If you do not have also within you some ability to transcend the goal transcend the success of the best. If you get to there, Steve look and see often in the parking lot behind the hideous bulging Neo Georgian cube of the community administration building. several small boys carrying and dragging white plastic bags, the nest of dumpsters that aborted the pines of the parking lots rear. The children pale and wild eyed and conferring among themselves and casting anxious looks across the grounds at the crowd behind the show court then puts her in court said and for the ones who do not become the law, The lucky who become profiled and photographed for readers and in the USA religion Make it They must have something built into them along the path that will let them transcend it or they are doomed. We see this and experience. One see this one sees this and all obsessive goal based cultures of pursuit, Look at the Jacqueline the law, the suicide rates of their later years. This task of us at the end field is more delicate still with the law for you, If you attain your goal and cannot find some way to transcend the experience of having that goal be your entire existence Your raison de fer. So then one of two things will happen. steeply had to keep breathing on the pen to keep the point thought one. One is that you attain the goal and realize the shocking realization that attaining the goal does not complete or redeem you does not make everything for your life Okay. As you are in the culture, educated to assume it will do this the goal And then you face this fact that what you had thought would have the meaning does not have the meaning when you get it and you are impaled by shock. We see suicides in history by people at these pinnacles the children here are versed in the what is called the saga of Eric Clapton with two peas Just so are the other possibility of doom for the XY who attain they attain the goal Thus, and put as much equal passion into celebrating their attainment as they had put into pursuing the attainment.
This is called here,
the syndrome of the endless party, The Celebrity money, sexual behaviors, drugs and substances, the glitter, they become celebrities instead of players. And because they are celebrities, only as long as they feed the culture of goals hunger, for the make it The winning, They are doomed, Because you cannot both because you cannot both because you cannot both celebrate and suffer. And play is always suffering.
Just so.
proclamation 4071 National clown week by Richard Nixon 37th President of the United States. Whoever has heard the laughter of a child or seen sudden delight on the face of a lonely old man has understood in those brief moments, mysteries deeper than love. All men are indebted to those who bring such moments of quiet splendor To redeem sickness and pain with joy all across America. Good Men and putty noses and baggy trousers following a tradition as old as man's need to touch gently the lives of his fellow man go into orphanages and children's hospitals, homes for the elderly and further retarded, and get a part of themselves. Today As always, clowns and the spirit they represent our is vital to the maintenance of our humanity, as the builders and the growers and the governors. And the folk Lord of the world, is that this it? In the folklore of the world is the persistent claim that the heart of a clown is sad, and that all the gladness he provokes, is simply a facade for the pain he cannot reveal to the world. And The myth is the kernel of reason. The clown leaves happiness where he goes
and takes misery away with him.
Yet, we cannot suppose there is real truth to the myth. For surely the laugh makers are blessed. They heal the heart of the world To call public attention to the charitable activities of clowns, and the wholesome entertainment they provide for all our citizens. The Congress by a joint resolution approved October 8 1970. Public Law 91 433 has requested the president to designate the week of august 1 through August 7 1971, as national clown week. Now therefore, I Richard M. Nixon, President of the United States of America, do hereby proclaim the week of august 1 through August 7 1971. As national clown week, I invite the governors of the states and the appropriate officials and other areas under the United States flag to issue similar proclamations. I urge the people of the United States to recognize contributions made by clowns and their entertainment at children's hospitals, charitable institutions, institutions for the mentally retarded, and generally helping to lift the spirits and boost the morale of our people. And witness Where have I have had their on to set my hand the second day of August, and the year of our Lord 1900 71 and of the independence of the United States of America, the 196 Richard Nixon
Happy dreams.