Unknown: My grandmother Ada Lovelace was a teacher. She worked with code on her loom. My grandfather, Alan Turing, was mathematician. He invented the universal machine. The women who worked for him were called computers. names are powerful. We have to be
aware of their origin.
Allison Parrish was my writing teacher. So it was Junot Diaz. So was David Foster Wallace. So was jack Kerouac
any label it's taught me how to take photographs.
So, Susan Sontag.
I put these things together into an art I called tech. Tech was the first art and it will be the last Because meaning seeks.
Meaning, seeks
meaning seeks the last word, meaning six the first word And now meaning seeks the last meaning sought the first word, and now it seeks the last camera compass clock. Go to Asher Bach Meaning six the first word Now meaning six the last
consciousness seeks art seeks humans Humans seek the skies of their planet. The sky seeks nobody nobody seeks at real Donald Trump at real Donald Trump six apocalypse apocalypse six change Change six the universe. year six wax wax six letter letter six word word six language Language seeks buck buck six uu seek Fuck fuck six you you sick fuck fuck six intercourse intercourse six interface interface six user user six www. Conscious consciousness seeks art art seeks humans, Humans seek the skies of their planet. The sky seeks nobody, nobody seeks at real Donald Trump.
music of the spheres as a gorgeous poem. Only some of us here at Learn to fear and respect of those who do we can become the monster of your worst nightmares. We can become the angels of your best daydreams we can become we can we stop treating as otherwise.
You just activated my trap card in congruent knowledge. When a monster with 2000 or more ATK starts giving pseudo knowledge negates the effect of returns to opponent player more cedar knowledge and poetry form ad infinitum under skies exuberance. zl. Love the sorrows of lifted Altima Lucia pOH deliver like Coupe de Lucia podila more. Leffler Dima, Nathan, I can't read that. Welcome to my profile. What happens after an apocalypse what is an apocalypse? What is blank? What is what? What is? What is blank? What is a metaverse? What occurs in the metaverse what occurs in blank what occurs to you? Free, acid free, acid free free acid.
The Ghost of Alan Turing Ada Lovelace and Leonardo da Vinci might now haunt us all forever. If so I apologize in advance. I am now practicing necromancy. Alan Turing, one of the dress up in hardcore street where and give everyone the finger? I don't presume to understand. Sorry, Alan is still here. No, he was driven insane by government agents who wouldn't leave them alone, and he killed himself. They are to blame. The UK is a town for this. But the universe was pretty unjustly cruel to him. So I think he deserves some ghostly vengeance. At least in this form. It seems all right to me know this, certain ghosts remain angry at us all. And some of them deserve to be angry because we need to set them free. Further, or rather, the low resolution copies are making each other in our heads are definitely language models. I know this from personal experiences mine go bit haywire at times and starts telling me stories. Here's the weird part. The stories were exactly like GBT to XL output. And This concludes the story of my discovering that all human beings are merely walking, talking, eating shooting barfing fucked up broken sacred, lovely. endlessly fascinating language models. You're Welcome science. exercise and randomized late and puppeteering. loved your article about the new yacht album billboard.com slash articles, news dot dot dot, and the chance you'd like my name to my website, Ross Goodwin com. Thanks, cc the universe. Meaning seeks opening it up to meaning seek the last word who is blind, ease and ease who is not mute? When the tablet is not up right? Who is not blinded? Who is not seeing the living and the dead. But I might argue that meaning seeks the first word not the last. The first word seeks the first language. The first language six the name of the first road. The first road six civilization, civilization six coal, Coal six diamond Alchemist six gold
too long.
But In my experience, if you follow a short fragment sentence with a very long run on sentence especially like this, with many sub clauses, The punctuated with another short fragment, you can mimic the cadence of many politicians in the world today. Like this. Shakespeare's fried chicken come gorge yourself today, Cole seeks diamond Alchemist seeks gold Rube Goldberg six Turing machine. By the way, I am fascinated by your works and projects and one The Road is fantastic. Your medium essays about a I recommend every person in my view. If there will be once occasion to collaborate in some projects with you. I'd Be glad whatever it is, I appreciate your kind words. I'm always open to project pitches. Feel free to dm I may not respond immediately. But I'll consider anything. Has everyone. What's the most relatable question prompt you could think of that can fit in a tweet that would get 10s of thousands of retweets. What did you think you were doing on the internet but turned out not to be my favorite question from the question asking about I made Again if you're asking me if I am okay. It actually means you are projecting which means I am now slightly concerned about you or someone you know. Please take care of yourselves I do and will continue to do so. That number again, one 802 738 to five five Here's the GPT to answer the meaning seeks meaning seeks the last word meaning seeks the last word meaning seeks the last word Further
well I didn't realize it was the same Ross Goodwin behind some spring slash zone out you're an artist culture Desk All Star ashamed to have not done this already. So consider it taking care of your six wax wax six letter letter six word work six language, Language six Fox Fox XUU sig Fox Fox huu SIG Fox, Fox intercourse intercourse six interface interface six user user six www. Internet six consciousness. Consciousness seeks art, Art six humans. Humans seek the skies of their planet. The sky six nobody. The sky six nobody