Unknown: We are voting for Barack Obama
are voting for Barack Obama.
uncertain times require a steady hand. Our country faces enormous challenges, a failed war, a crippling deficit and an economy in crisis. We live in uncertain times. And we need a president with sound judgment and steady leadership. That's why millions of Republicans across our country are rejecting the divisive politics of the past. We are voting for Barack Obama, because we are serious about getting our governments long term finances in order, putting our economy back on track, ending the war in Iraq responsibly and keeping America safe. Because brock obama is bringing us all together to reject the karl rove School of wedge politics And fundamentally changed the way Washington works. Because even though we're proud to be Republicans, We are Americans first. Now is the time for Americans to stand together. Our country faces enormous challenges. And We simply cannot afford more the same republicans for Obama newspaper at USA Today, Tuesday, October 28 2008. June 5 2009, Massachusetts Institute of Technology upon the recommendation of the faculty here by confers on Ross Evan Goodwin, the degree of Bachelor of Science and economics and recognition of proficiency in the general and the special studies and exercises prescribed by said Institute for such degree given the standing under the seal of the Institute of Cambridge, and the Commonwealth of Massachusetts.
sciences and Hartfield, President of MIT.
Artificial Intelligence requires us to go further. It requires more of humanity. It requires us to be better. Because AI is like the camera. It's like the typewriter. It's like the compass. It's like the clock. It's like all of the inventions combined makes them all better. It makes them all smarter. And We have to stop neglecting. The last word is further
Crimson flames like Purple Rain. These terrapins Blaze, The Purple Haze and affects my brain. All synapse rage. These lightning strikes from year to year and page to page, year to year and age to age. Tied through
since high school.
A high fence these wire tools They cut through like butter, But another's behind it. You'll find land mines abandoned from another time. from other times inside each line, I'll be fine So long as I find the next rhyme.
I fear my ears burnin tears fallen
rolling high in the saddle, fighting back and mighty traps still an idol in this knapsack mounted force hopes like thunder claps drove our fears down Countless with fire on flaming roads using ideas as my maps
losing them the tall grass past the flask and split up
This loot of legend will meet on I just seen said I lay low until then go to the law and you'll be writing your own. Oh bet.
It's your closed casket funeral.
If you blow this racket or a whistle, Nobody needs to know what went down. Got it. Understand. You see. I'm proud need heated brown all y'all. But I was so much older than I'm younger than that now. But I was so much older than I'm younger than that now.
But I was so much older than
I'm younger than that now.
Meaning is overrated.
Meaning is overrated. Street View is not shuttle to us.
There's just automating emotional response detection.
Half rack These fat stacks, mathematic clap traps, like flat taxes. regressive measures the Max Headroom, broadcast intrusion, forecast collusion, prejudice against progressive mindsets. All Time highs, stock markets leaped forth to rise and rise until speculative forces surmise the false common It's a run on the bank. Your stock tank deflated your buck lost its over your hard earned greens now lining pockets of one percenters who profit from the same financial instability that ruins normal folks, makes them lose their jobs and jump from Windows. Fuck Trump and everyone complicit in the system. I said rip down all hate, I screamed lies that life is black and white. spoke from my skull. I dreamed a dream that pulled me closer. So light the match, Toss it on the trail of kerosene That leads to romantic facts of musketeers foundation deep somehow. But I was so much older than I'm younger
than that now.
In a soldier stance to foreign lands am 16 and hand Every problem becomes a nail when your hammer fires, lead, subjugate and obfuscate at your generals command. Just know he takes his orders from a man who doesn't read, whose biggest claim to fame. It's huge was reality TV, who put his cronies and family and every seat of power in the land. And they're all business criminals, so I won't say his name again. In fact, instead, I am my hand down toward the earth shot up bullet in the ground to symbolize rebirth. But now I found that nothing grows from this kind of seed, Step pain and hurt and body counts. And those don't count as trees. So I went to university screamed at the mongrel dogs who teach economics, politics and cultural studies. Fearing Not that I become another PhD, who asks his country why it fights in wars that no one needs. It takes no partner action his democracy allows the poor to die in wars the rich believe they need Instead of resisting the system, and ink or act or deed, Fearing not the people over the authorities that I become my enemy, And the instant that I preach, Put your bodies upon the gears and upon the wheels of the machine. Sisters fled by confusion boats mutiny from certain to bow Ah, but I was so much older than I'm younger than that now. My guards dead hardwood abstract art became our only means of expression because the sensors outlawed every other thing called it zombies dot degenerate or unAmerican Said threats to freedom everywhere will vanish in the haze. Once we eliminate their voices, and outlaw their rage. The only source now locked away inside an iron cage. And only subjects appropriate were spared the Crimson flames, religious iconography and military scenes that demonstrate wars glory with imagery to nobles neglect of horses, Tall Ships cavalry, Nobody dying yet. The stars and stripes are billowing upon the castle walls deceived me into thinking I had something to protect. Good and bad and I find these terms quite clear, no doubt somehow. But I was so much older than I'm younger than that now.