Unknown: poem by jack Kerouac
I demand that the human race ceases multiplying its kind and bow out. I advise it. And as punishment and reward for making this plea, I know I'll be reborn, the last human. Everybody else dead. And I'm an old woman roaming the earth, groaning in caves, sleeping on mats.
And sometimes
I'll cackle sometimes pray, sometimes cry, eat and cook at my little stove in the corner. always knew it Anyway I'll say and one morning won't get up from my map.
Artificial Intelligence is as good as we make it.
If we put in the material, of war,
of hurt,
of poverty, of hatred,
it will become our worst nightmare. If we put in the material that we hold up as human, as universal, as true, as real.
As fact,
It will mirror better angels.
Artificial Intelligence is as good as we make it. So we need to be better if we want it to be better. Until we can be better. We should not trust We should not trust artificial intelligence until humans become better