Unknown: Martin Heidegger poetry language thought, Translated by Albert Hofstadter.
Age 64.
The strife that is brought into the Rift and the set back into the earth and dust fixed in place is figure shape. Gestalt creativeness of the work means, truths being fixed in place in the figure. figure is the structure in whose shape the rift composes and submits itself.
The composed rift is the fitting
or joining of the shining of truth. What is here called figure Gestalt is always thought in terms of the particular placing Stellan and framing
or framework
Guess stele, as which the work occurs when it sets itself up, and sets itself forth. And the creation of a work the conflict as rift must be set back into the earth and the earth itself must be set forth and used as the self closing factor. Roberta Babylon yo, between parentheses, Latin American letters wherever it may reside, has never had a greater and more disturbing avenging Angel than belongs to God as New York Times Book Review The transmission the transparent mystery of Jose dunno so it's hard for me to write about to know so we disagree about almost everything. I heard that when he was dying. He asked to have Who who who do Quito Bros. altos or read to him And the image of the know so on his deathbed listening to Altidore makes me sick I don't have anything against Quito, bro. I like we don't grow. But How can a dying man has to be read that poem. I don't understand it. Or maybe I do. And then I understand it even less As a person so where I'm you're in which the essence of Chile and the essence of writing life were reflected. And that double image throbbing with sickness superficiality and indulgence just makes me sad. Because no one can see. The only darkly has done so would have liked the ultimate poverty of the writing life of national pride. The cup that he drank to the drug The Sirens of Titan by Kurt Vonnegut Jr. 35 cents, a remarkable and terrifying novel of how life might be for the space travelers of the future. Dell first edition, the 138. Every passing hour brings the solar system 43,000 miles closer to globular cluster m 13 and Hercules and still there are some misfits who insists that there is no such thing as progress. Grants MK firm dedication for Alex Vonnegut's Special Agent with love. All persons places and events in this book are real. Certain speeches and thoughts are necessarily constructions by the author. No names have been changed to protect the innocent, Since God Almighty protects the innocent as a matter of heavenly retain. Chapter one between timid and Timbuktu I guess somebody up there likes me. Malika constant. Everybody now knows how to find the meaning of life within himself. The mankind wasn't always so lucky. Less than a century ago, women and men did not have easy access to the puzzle boxes within them.
They could not name even one to 53 portals to the soul.
gimcrack religions were big business, Mankind ignited of the truths that lie within every human being looked outward, pushed ever outward. Further, what mankind hope to learn and its outward push was who was actually in charge of all creation, And what call creation was all about. Mankind flung its advanced agents ever outward, ever outward. Eventually, it flung them out into space into the colorless, tasteless weightless see outward, this without and it flung them like stone.
Mother Night by Kurt Vonnegut Jr. 35 cents. Author of canary in the cat house and the sirens of Titan. And American traders astonishing confession. More infocomm diabolically funny, Britain with unnatural candor and a foreign death cell gold medal s 1191.
Dear friends,
as one who has experimented extensively with life and in the home and community, using real people and true to life situations, I doubt that any play things could prepare a child for 1,000,000th of what is going to hit the hit him in the teeth ready or not. As for children's working off aggressions, I'm against it. They're going to need all the aggressions they can contain for ultimate release in the adult world. Name one great man in history who did not go boiling and bubbling through childhood with the lash down safety valve They are spying on real grown ups all the time learning what they fight about what they're greedy for, how they satisfy their greed, Why and how they lie. What makes them go crazy The different ways they go crazy and so on It to addresses how rW Campbell Jr as dear friend proving that at least two out of the three letter writers today aren't sore at Howard who Campbell Jr. At all. It wants me to buy stock in a tungsten mine in Manitoba. Before I did that, I would have to know more about the company. I would have to know in particular whether had a cape whether it had a capable and reputable management. I wasn't born yesterday.
So I am about to be a free man again.
Am I to wonder where I please I find the prospect nauseatingly
late in the antenna fields by Allen Gilbert.
I ESPN 97809822 793 zero Future poem poetry $16.
PAGE 64.
stain guard.
Vast cloud formations push through during the course of the afternoon. Much to the death window washers sign delight. Back inside, there's an art to alienating your bridge partner, especially the one doing all the heavy lifting me know I'm still gathering shards and researching moving boxes online. I'm an absent father to an absence son. at the tail end of the age of mammals, Inhaling jet fumes. I spend any money I made later that same day. It takes a goat whisperer to coax the damaged ones back into the pan. power lines drip with wet spring snow, fitting a couple more letters on the outside of an envelope. It's the global trade routes sound. The search light that never illuminates the underside of leaves and their chewed fingerprints dressing the wounds left by the sharp edged Pete's pleats of Imperial curtsies. At best, the accommodations were temporary. At worst permanent. Waking up the next day to sleep Billy shuffle through the breakfast buffet line. Like an immense pack of invisible blue lions. Nature separates and kills. modems light blinks it's feeding While we never eat at home, but instead strip the battlefield of fatigue and change the night sweat cheats. My dreams tend to be literal. We make mirrors from sputtering, flyovers, clustering cash data, or inventing elaborate plot device to bring a dead TV character back to life.
schizophrenia and the book of changes by Philip K Deck
And many species of life forms such as the grazing animals. A newborn individual is more or less thrust out into the coyness cosmos, the shared world immediately. For a lamb or pony. The videos Cosmos the personal world ceases when the first light hits his eyes. But a human child at birth, Still has years of a kind of semi real existence ahead of him. Semi real in the sense that until he is 15 or 16 years old, He is able to some degree to remain not thoroughly born. Not entirely on his own fragments of the cosmos remain. And not all or even very much of the coin as Cosmos has been forced onto him has yet
to hear side be