Unknown: Medical Pennsylvania, New York New York, Portland, Oregon,
London, England, Sydney, Australia
3838 77 AL Cannock explosion smoke steam and stones from a crater of us Yama, Yama, Japan.
You are up on the summit of the largest volcano in Japan close to the circular brink of the crater which is almost three quarters of a mile and circumference. The man at the left is an English friend of his hunger for the other is a Japanese Coolio accompany the party to carry extra baggage. That ladder strapped on his back is when frequently used in order to hold the camera higher than the surrounding level. The site you now see is what the photographer's camera recorded recorded on a summer day in 1903. He says that this very experience While we were at the summit of a terrible explosion occurred, and thousands of tons of rocks were ejected many hundreds of feet into the air far above us. Mr. tues hat was blown off by a sudden explosion. Indeed, we narrowly escaped with our lives for rocks, many of them weighing half a ton or more fell all around us. After the explosion a great column of thick black smoke rose probably three miles into the air. I ran after and caught my camera Cooley who was fleeing for his life and made these negatives You're looking north from the south side of the craters edge After hastily making these negatives we had to leave for the volcano was evidently in a very angry mood extract from report to the publisher.
Nazi ism in the high Castle I Philip K Deck
many moons have passed since white man iE Powell Anderson review my book man in the high castle and fen eg too many to note with However, one exception of certain john Boardman have commented, not on the book nor review per se, but on Nazi ism, which is right and proper, because that is the true topic, far more so than any novel or any review and only proves that I am right. We are still very much afraid, still rightly so very much disturbed. And as Harry Warner so correctly said, we might identify with the war guilt of the Germans because they're so similar to us. However, although these comments etc, took place back in March, I have just now seen them and would also like to comment. The Digital wristwatch a Philip K Deck by Richard A lop off page 11. She was gone. He was alone. He wondered if he could jump from the Seiko wristwatch to the mobile one premium giveaway. But he decided against making the attempt, There seemed little point in it. If he succeeded, he would be no better off than he was already. And if he failed, That might spell his final dissolution. He didn't want to risk it. Instead, he made a serious effort to look around. He discovered that he could sense his surroundings. He wasn't sure whether he was really seeing or not. In fact, the boundaries of all his senses had disappeared, And he was merely aware of the Gestalt of his surroundings. He inferred that his electrical field was interacting with the electrical totality of his surroundings, that he was consequently, being tugged into the shape congruent with the field of those surrounding. By examining himself, he was therefore able to study everything around him. conceivably, If you were perceptive enough, he could comprehend the Universe by merely examining himself. thought was particular peculiar, But he didn't know where he was. He was on a wrist, And the rest was picking up a telephone. Film at supreme effort. He locked away from the wristwatch and fled toward the telephone. There was a moment of complete blackness and absolute cold. And then he was plunging into a network of circuitry that ran from the handset along the telephone wire to the cradle, and it's crude matrix. he sped onward. Further through the walls of the building Along the wires to the Fullerton switching, exchange, Feeling himself stretched, energized, boosted tour, He came to a halt deep in the guts of a massive switching computer somewhere in the center of Greater Los Angeles. There were others around him, thousands of others.
Welcome brother or sister.
If On a winter's night a traveler by a telenovela
translators note in chapter eight the passage from crime and punishment is quoted in the book The love translation of constants garden at WW One you are about to begin reading a tele Kelby and his new novel upon a winter's night a traveler, Relax, Concentrate, dispel every other thought. Let the world around you fade. Best to close the door. The TV is always on in the next room. tell the others right away. No, I don't want to watch TV. Raise your voice. They won't hear you. Otherwise, I'm reading. I don't want to be disturbed. Maybe they haven't heard you. With all that racket. Speak louder yell. I'm beginning to read Italo Calvino, his new novel, or if you prefer, Don't say anything. Just hope they'll leave you alone. Find the most comfortable position seated stretched out curled up or lying flat, flat on your back on your side on your stomach. In an easy chair on the sofa in the rocker, the deck chair on the hammock in the hammock. If you have a hammock, On top of your bed, of course, we're in the bed. You can even stand on your hands head down in the yoga position. With the book upside down naturally. Of course, the ideal position for reading is something you can never find. In the old days they used to read standing up at the lectern. People were accustomed to standing on their feet without moving. They rested like that when they were tired of horseback riding. Nobody ever thought of reading on horseback and yet now, The idea of sitting in the saddle The book propped against the horse's mane or may be tied to the horses a year with a special harness seemed attractive to you. With your feet in the stirrups just feel quite comfortable for reading. Having your feet up is the first condition for enjoying a read. Well What are you waiting for, stretch your legs go ahead and put your feet on a cushion on to cushions On the arms over the sofa on the wings of the chair on the coffee table on the desk on the piano on the globe. Take your shoes off first If you want to put your feet up if not put them back. Don't stand there with your shoes in one hand and the book and the other Adjust the light so you won't strain your eyes. Do it now because once you're absorbed in reading there will be no budget you make sure the pages and shadow accounting of black letters on a gray background uniform as a pack of mice But Be careful the light cast on it isn't too strong doesn't glare on the cruel light of the paper Nine at the shadows of the letters as in a southern now noon day Try to foresee now everything that might make you interrupt your reading cigarettes within reach If you smoke in the ashtray Anything else you have to pay all right, you know best
poem is by Ray Bradbury, The Haunted computer and the Android Pope
Haunted computer Android Pope One source data The other hope The late night ghosts of man's dire needs are snacks on which computer feeds to harvest Ciro's some the sun's knock Something Wicked Eric come and drop dumb evil to its knees with electric snicker sneeze Well Android Pope takes up from there were physics stops mid flight mid air. Their Papa's primed electric mind grows faith in countries of the blind where massive gravity bulk huge Andromeda is centrifuge or metal matter dwindles to me or flee their Android Postmates penalty to serve to doubtful Thomas me And the and dine and dine in the Last Supper is his two circuit there were physically physics loses self and air and man surprised by larger small She's not beyond the to at all.
Turn the tape to listen to decide. Be